♪ In the not too distant future
♪ Next Sunday, A.D.
♪ There was a guy named Joel
♪ Not too different
from you or me.
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute,
♪ just another face
in red jumpsuit
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place,
♪ but his bosses didn't like him
♪ so they shot him into space
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies
♪ The worst we
can find, la-la-la
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all,
♪ And we'll monitor
his mind la-la-la
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control
♪ Where the movies
begin or end (la-la-la)
♪ Because he used
those special parts
♪ To make his robot friends.
♪ Robot roll call Cambot
♪ Gypsy, hi girl
♪ Tom Servo, what a cool guy
♪ Crow, wisecracker
♪ You're wondering how
he eats and breaths
♪ and other science facts
♪ then repeat to
yourself it's just a show
♪ I should really just relax
♪ for Mystery Science
Theater 3000
(doors creaking shut)
So I'll tell you later, ok.
Hi everybody, welcome
to the Satellite Love
my name is Joel Robinson,
these are my robots Crow
T-Robot, and Tom Servo.
What you guys doing?
Well we were just
trying to remember
what it was that Bunny Rabbit
used to always try to get
Captain Kangaroo to say.
Oh uh, ping pong balls.
(Robots cheering and giggling)
Good one! Alright!
Wow, those have been
up there for months!
Every time it rains and rains!
Commercial sign in 5, 4, 3, 2.
Help me.
I got Crow-T Robot eyes.
I'll say, hi Crow,
what you doin?
I can't find my eyes!
Oh, have you
looked over there?
Oh thanks, I didn't think.
Would you just, I
don't have any eyes.
(Servo cackling)
Jeepers creepers, Tom
you got Crow's peepers
now give them back.
Tom gimme those, can't you
see what I'm going through.
Why yes I can see
as a matter of fact,
I can see better than ever.
Quiet you guys, Sunny, Terry,
and Brownie McGee are calling.
♪ I sing whenever I
sing whenever I sing
Quit clowning around up there
and get on with the invention
exchange, crocodile kangaroo.
Well sirs, our invention
exchange this week
is based on the premise
that more and more people
are becoming vegetarians,
this means warehouses full of
gamey forest beef products.
What are you gonna do
with all that steak?
Make a fun friend.
Like this little guy,
Mr. Meat and Potato Head.
That's rare, isn't it?
We've taken the Mr.
Potato Head concept
and fleshed it out.
Literally.
For example, here's beef
spokesman James Garner
as Mr. Brisket Head
and he comes with his own
little Rockford Camaro.
And of course there's
the suave and continental
Sir Beef Wellington Head.
Oh is the great Sir
Beef Wellington Head
gonna grace us
with his presence?
Yeah and for all
those smart shoppers
that have already
been vegetarians
there's Mr. Stuffing
Instead of Potato Head.
What do you think, sirs?
Stuffing instead of potatoes?
Honey, I love you!
Meat is Murder, Frank.
Speaking of conserving
waste, just because your
British pop sensation's
career has gone stale,
doesn't mean that he has to.
That's why we've invented
the Tupperware container
to lock-in pop star freshness.
Who's our stale singing
sensation, Frank?
Well it's none other than
British popstar, Morrissey.
He's a little depressed.
So Morrissey, how you doing?
You hurt me with that remark,
did I mention that I cried?
Well I mean come
on, Morrissey,
we're basically evil, granted,
but a lot of what
we say around here
is just good-natured ribbing.
Well it hurt me, did I
mentioned that I cried?
Is it wrong not
to always be glad?
Well we seem to have
got you at a bad time.
Like Morrissey, Joel,
your experiment this week
comes from that shameful
decade known as the 80s.
It's a film called City Limits
and it stars James Earl
Jones at the low point
in his career and Kim
Catrall at a high point.
It also has Robbie Benson
and Rae Dawn Chong
doing things they're not
happy with either,
and now to prove that
our Tupperware coffin
really locks in
pop-star freshness,
Morrissey's going to
honor us with a song,
aren't you Morrissey?
This is a song I wrote
at a time in my life
when I was very, very, very sad,
breakfast actually,
it's called
Hairdresser in a Coma.
♪ I cried last night,
I died a million deaths
♪ thinking of your sweet face
♪ and the way you sing
♪ I cried inside,
we lied and died
♪ and then I cried again
♪ I must have wept for
hours cause I couldn't cry
(muffled singing)
(spaceship beeping)
We've got movie sign!
City Limits, sounds
like a clothing store
for high school girls.
15 years from now,
Dick Clark will
still look the same.
Wow this film moves fast,
a minute ago we
were in the credits,
now we're 15 years
in the future!
Well 15 years from now
is really depressing.
Well they still
have Super America.
Ok, we're at Grandma's,
wake up, come on.
That's a lot of fabric
to wear on a cycle.
Someone's been diggin in
the remnant pile big time.
(gunshot firing)
Oh, Austin City Limits.
I said it's prepay after ten.
Leland!
This is CNN, get off my land.
Ok, it's ok.
Oh it's the Doc
Severenson gang.
Hey I found Ed Begley
Jr. can I keep him?
Where are we?
At home.
Oh there's no place like
home for the holocaust.
Oh, Mr. Potato Head.
I know it's CNN right, uh uh.
Damn boy, I told
you to find adventure.
I didn't say drag it home.
These are the clippers.
No don't hit me
Mr. Earl Jones!
[James Earl Jones] If I'd
known what he was getting into
I never would have let him go.
He's throwing his voice,
his a ventriloquist.
We were not the kind
to run without a fight.
And by the looks of
it, he and his friends
had taken the beating.
Jill Kinmont, in the
other side of the movie.
I'd raised Leland
since the plague
took his parents.
Hey turn the bass down!
Oh, that's his voice.
Most of the adults were
killed by the plague,
and left a world of orphans
to die off from lack of care.
They were known
as the bitter ones.
You know just when you get
good at skiing, it's
spring, isn't it,
ain't that the way.
He had me to help him along,
together we came through okay.
Hey it's becoming a
Windham Hill album cover.
We lived by ourselves
away from the troubles for years
but finally it was time for
him to make his own life.
So I cut him lose
to find adventure.
Hi there, heh.
That's not Rae Dawn Chong.
I don't think so.
Stop or the horse
gets it, I mean it!
Hi, I'm next killer.
Kim Catrall, oh.
I can't get there, they
keep freeze framing me!
I know what you're
saying, nice skull.
Don't be afraid
I'm just big boned.
Ew.
I liked the skull better.
I'd say he's out
of his skull now.
(giggling)
I'm gonna get me a
piece of bottom land.
Someday this'll all be ours,
oh it is ours.
Petticoat Junction.
Yeah this movies moving
slower than Uncle Joe.
Would you guys mind
if I opened my umbrella here,
you never know when
something, you know,
Oh for crying out loud.
Is this impolite
to keep it open
to keep the umbrella open
while we're...
Hey, we gotta drink
out of that water!
Where you going?
I'm going to the city.
Going to get you some clothes!
What for?
Because I wanna be a clipper.
There's no such
thing as a clipper.
He got dressed awful fast.
Yeah, there is.
Well I'm nude so nevermind.
Hey wear your other skull,
we need to rinse that one out.
He's gonna leave all of this?
Hey, my clothes!
I guess you could call
this Cheesy Rider.
They must have a
mandatory skull law.
Robbie Benson, oh!
♪ Goldfinger, Warren Goldberg
Hey, we found the title!
[James Earl Jones] He
was heading for the city.
- He had an idea in his head
- In his skull.
That there was new life there.
The kids had banded together
and survived by scavenging
and foraging in the
deserted streets.
After the robot holocaust.
These kids were
called the clippers,
and Leland was out to find them.
And they were a real
sharp gang, real boosters.
They used to be
called the cost cutters.
♪ All my fingers,
butterfingers
It looks like the
sets were designed by
- Edward Hopper.
- Franke Gary.
Look, apparently they're
trying to pass this off
as being written.
There's gotta be a cash
machine around here somewhere.
Filmed on location in
Mazomanie, Wisconsin,
over by the new high school.
Sounds like "Love Me Do."
(robots humming theme music)
He's giving himself a ticket.
I can't get this
through my thick skull.
Whoa!
Uh, you're really stupid
if you get hit by a car
after the apocalypse.
(motorcycle revving)
Oh I get it,
soundtrack by Gerry Rafferty.
Oh darn it's copyrighted.
Oh look it's Louis the
Fourteenth's warehouse.
The Sun King, you know.
But Leland no idea that
there was a new sickness
- in the city.
- It's called apathy, man.
Outsiders, sent
in to take control.
- Kim Catrall!
- Hey, take it easy.
Hey I'm not really
a skull, lady!
I'm not really an actress.
- May we help you?
- Yeah, I'd like her.
Move away from your vehicle.
It's the Orkan army.
And there will be
lots more exciting
scenes like this.
Anybody got a clue
what this is about?
The chief's phone!
(gasps)
I wonder what the red one means.
1-900-TALK-TO-ROBBIE,
this is Robbie Benson,
what are you wearing?
Uh yeah, your girlfriend just
threw something off a bridge.
- I'm sure it's nothing.
- Make sure it's taken care of.
Ok, yes sir.
Boy I like my
after-school paper route,
it's so great I get
this cool helmet
and it's great.
The three bikers
of the apocalypse!
Hey, are you guys clippers?
No, we're color consultants.
Oh there must be a chain gang.
Was that a yes?
Hey, Red Skeleton.
(chuckling)
Courageous cat
and motor mouse.
They're trying to kill
me, I guess I'll park.
You thought that was
scary, what about this!
Haha.
How are you?
Oh I make a nice living, you?
Out of line.
- Hey, Ernie!
- Yeah, Bert?
Send him back.
Fish it, Bert.
It is Bert and Ernie.
Gotta go, gotta go.
(Crow laughing maniacally)
He's being terrorized
by the cast of Fame.
Something wrong?
Is this your engine?
(alarm sounding)
The queen!
Broach coach.
Bring out your dead!
Uh oh, it's the Leno gang.
Oh damn, we over shot him.
It's so freaking dark
we couldn't see him.
The clippers.
Leathers by Bob Mackie.
How you doing?
He's the one,
this is superman?
Shaken, not stirred.
It's little Bobbi Hepburn.
You'll wanna wash that hand.
He's wearing a sheep.
How come you're wearing a sheep?
The sheep didn't
need it no more.
(loud laughter)
The sheep didn't
need it no more!
Maplethorpe?
I got something for you guys.
What, what's that?
Me!
(laughter)
Ha, we already
have one of you!
Where are you from?
- I'm from the desert.
- On a horse with no name?
Okay.
What?
Hey I come a lot of miles!
For a lot of camels.
Riding on a couple prey pigs
don't make you a clipper.
Hey those are my parents!
We ain't looking for nobody.
Yeah, the position's filled.
You'd be bored, it's
mostly data entry.
Even if we was, these
kids was born here.
Oh, that's Michelle Shocked.
What did you expect?
Balloons?
You need a concept
wardrobe, like me!
Come on, Frankie,
off the bike.
Well so what was that whole
hitting me with chains
thing all about?
That's a super
charger on there.
Super super charger.
Go on home, cowboy.
Uh so, do you think your dad
could sign my Big Bamboo album?
Wow look at what
he's missing out on.
All this.
It's the guys from Kansas.
There's a big pile
of Bob right there.
Ok, five minutes everyone!
Oh it's heavy, oh,
oh oh it's heavy.
That guy's a big Who fan.
Looks like a Bay
City Roller guy.
Hey, England wants
its flag back!
Hey, hey you got a name?
Yeah I got a name.
Harley Davidson
and the Marlboro Man.
I want it, I want it,
I want it, I want it.
Uh oh, mandatory bussing.
Looks like you're
over the line, Bert.
Are we?
One toke.
That moog killed Bob.
Shut up.
- Is he a clipper?
- What about Bob?
(grunting)
Oh, now he's a
Vienna Boy's Clipper.
Ouch, oh.
Are you okay?
I can walk.
(grunting)
It's the Candy Striper gang!
Physician, heal thyself, haha.
Let's go!
(squealing)
I can't get down, I'm
stuck up here, help me!
You meet the nicest
people on a Honda.
(suspenseful music)
Chips, 15 years from now.
Boxes!
Sounds like every
Kenny Loggins song.
I'm tired of the
running and the hiding.
Footloose!
Oh geeze, I told you to floss.
Okay, you can puke now.
(laughing)
Geeze, I lose an arm
you'll really crack up.
You're bleeding on my blazer.
This guys just funny,
he can't explain it,
he can't explain
it, he's just funny.
I'll pass a stone in a minute,
that'll make you howl.
My name, Yogi.
You know, picnic
basket, Boo Boo, all that staff.
I'm Lee.
Where are we going?
Oh, we're going to
hell in a handbasket.
You know if they
were to drive in
better lit areas they wouldn't
they wouldn't run
into such hoodlums.
You're right, this is neat!
♪ Purple rain, purple rain ♪
Oh, a prop shop!
Hey Mick!
These are for you, we
found a whole bunch
down by the tunnel.
The clown shoes are in!
All you gotta do is
cut the toe part off.
Hey talk to Scooter,
he's got big feet.
Scooter, he's funny!
Get outta here. They're
your girlscout cookies.
(men bickering)
Hey, hey, hey, what's this?
This is food.
It's pussy nibbles.
It's good.
Oh come on, this
is so offensive
on so many levels.
We don't eat cat food.
Why not?
Cause we ain't cats!
See the first thing
is, cats have four feet,
and they've got fur.
I thought I'd give
you guys another chance.
What happened?
We had a terrible day.
Yeah?
Oh, you shoulda been there.
Where'd she get that
Liz Claiborne suit
in the apocalypse?
He killed dirty Bob.
What?
Hold it, hold it!
Let's take this out.
I miss Kim.
(doors creaking shut)
Hello, good day,
happy to see you.
I, Crow T. Robot have
penned a little ditty
in honor of the star
of today's experiment,
Kim Catrall.
It's called Oh Kim Catrall,
by Crow T. Robot.
Sung by Crow T. Robot.
It's marked Allegro con brio,
Köchel listing 643.
♪ Kim Catrall, Kim Catrall,
♪ Kim Kim Kim Kim Kim Catrall
♪ You were in Mannequin and
that was a really good movie
♪ Kim Cattrall Kim Cattrall
Kim Cattrall Kim Cattrall!
Kim Cattrall Kim Cattrall
♪ Kim Kim Kim Cattrall
♪ You've never made a bad film
♪ Oh what the
hell, ring my bell,
♪ let's go to the dells,
♪ our relationship will gel
♪ I like your smell,
you're really swell
♪ I'm Charlton
Heston for con-tell
♪ I love you, Kim
♪ I liked your dress
at the Ace awards
♪ Cattrall!
And now, a short scene from
Mannequin by Crow-T Robot.
Well, I didn't really
write it, I wish I had.
Anyway, ok, are you guys ready?
- Ready.
- Alright, hit it.
Switcher, switcher?
Oh, Joel, do the voice,
you're ruining it for me!
Oh, ok, uh,
Switcher you are one sick puppy,
after him Rambo.
Woof, woof.
Ok, now quick, go get into
your James Spader costume.
Switcher, I am going
to clean your clock.
- I kind of like that, it's
pretty good isn't it.
- Come on, play right!
- I'll never leave you!.
- Oh Gypsy, not yet.
Swticher you are
one sick puppy.
Switcher!
Lemme try to explain
this real slowly.
We've got a truce.
Those are the boundaries.
Now a truce has got rules.
Rules, and knife fights?
No guns, we don't use
them, they don't use them.
Hey look in the
back it's the audience
interest curve.
No more killing.
Hey that guy was chasing me.
Yeah but you were
over in his territory.
Ray's gonna want him back.
What?
Ray's the head of the DAs.
The shaggy DAs?
Well I don't care who he is,
you tell him he can't have me.
You just can't do that!
You're not even a clipper,
you're just a mook.
You're nothing.
Oh yeah, well
you're a dumb head.
Back where you came
from you may be something.
Naw not really,
pretty much squat there too.
I don't see any other way
but to give you up to him.
Hey Mick, you ever read
Insect Man number 47?
Oh yeah it's a really
good, great, graphic novel.
An eye for an eye.
Tooth for a tooth.
Look, make money selling grit.
Oh, maybe.
What?
Ok, go get Ray.
Tell him we got
the cowboy for him.
Oh, the movie's gonna
get confusing now.
We're gonna have to
make this look good.
It's Huggy Bear!
And the Calvolkee Kids.
Hello I'm Antonio Fargis,
I'll be your foppish
foil for the next hour.
- Ray.
- Mick.
What'd you call me?
Here he is.
Ladies and gentleman,
David Copperfield!
He don't look like much.
He ain't.
We wrapped him up for
you and everything, Ray.
That's nice.
Why don't you
have a seat, Ray?
Naw, we gotta go.
We got...we got
a wedding to go to.
Ray, do you ever
read Insect Man?
Whitey, you don't
take you arm off us
- we're gonna break it.
- Us?
We feeling a little
cranky, Sybil?
Of course.
We read them all.
We've got the biggest
collection in the city.
What about 47?
That's the one with Boomerang.
That's 42.
That's where Jughead
eats a lot of hamburgers.
Okay, 47, is the one
were this alien guy
goes to the city and by
accident kills a guy, right?
And they don't know
what to do with him,
so they set up this---
Contest.
Your best guy against him.
Forgot your line,
here's the script.
I can't read, I just
like all the bright colors.
Dirty Bob was a
personal friend of ours.
It'll be like the old days.
Yeah back when
movies had plots.
Alright.
He wins, you keep him.
- He loses...
- You keep him.
- we do what we want with him.
- Starting with the nasty.
But, we get to keep this.
No!
Mine's getting kind of old.
Sorry to hear that.
Now that I'm
removed from this,
it all seems so absurd.
Days Inn, where
all our rooms are
Do Not Disturb.
Hey your jerry curls arrived.
Ok, people, places
everyone, here we go.
Ok let's see your
grammar stinks,
your punctuation is
atrocious, B minus.
You been waiting
for a long time?
Where's Carver?
Mr. Carver is a
very busy man, Ray.
So am I.
It's a little late
for script revisions.
How are you doing
with the clippers?
Great, no more nose hairs!
I'm handling that now.
Just tell Carver
the clipper's gonna be
in our territory tomorrow.
We're having a game.
Husker du, in Norwegian means,
do you remember.
Good, I'll have
Wickings talk to them.
I'm so angry I
could just spit.
Uh, Ray?
Uh, did you get your lollipop,
there's a free one
for you right here.
How much does
he know about us?
I've been very discreet.
Nothing.
From what you say about him
I don't expect Wickings
to have much success.
Mick will come around.
He's not stupid.
So you say, and I
hope you're right.
- Our
relationship depends on it.
- That and mutual contempt.
I'm not interested
in half a city.
Do you understand?
He'll come around.
Good.
I'll see you tomorrow then.
It's a date.
(robots humming along
with soundtrack)
Oh now that's
downright disrespectful.
Oh at least they're
going to the library.
It's Paul Revere
and the Raiders.
(robots whistling)
So the future is
ruled by vicious fops,
is that what we're
supposed to believe here?
Hello, I am Inigo Montoya.
He is dreamy.
(robots glugging)
Don't pollute.
- Mick.
- Ray.
How's the hat party going?
I got a surprise for you Mick.
Aw, gee thanks and I
didn't get you anything.
This is Wickings, she's from--
Is this a pull?
This is Mick.
Mick.
Go ahead, pull
her finger it's fun.
I understand that
you're going to have
some kind of a contest here.
Yeah, did you
bring your t-shirt?
I don't want to take
up too much of your time.
I represent the
Sunya corporation.
The who?
And we're hired by
the federal government.
Oh, this is a pull.
To restore essential
services in your area.
Now, what this means.
Lady, we ain't stupid.
Nobody's calling
anybody stupid, Mick.
Not on screen, anyway.
Now, wait a second.
Tell them about the lights.
Look, after you're done here
why don't you ride
over and see what we're
doing on Ray's side.
There's going to be
medicine and food.
And party favors.
And you rememebr what
the city used to be like?
We're going to
light it up again.
- Like Broadway.
- Shh, let her speak.
I don't remember no lights.
that was before my time.
Before yours too maybe.
You're being stupid, Mick.
Indiana Jones and
the Temple of Goons?
Lady nobody gives
nothing for nothing.
Except Billy Preston.
What about the game?
- Are we gonna have the
game or not?
- Scattegories.
What's the matter Ray?
None of your guys want to play?
Come on, where's
your school spirit?
Can I say something?
No.
Everybody shut up,
Kim's gonna say something!
Ok, go ahead Kim.
Ray?
Salieri.
(foreboding music)
It's one of those
Flowbee haircutters.
For me? Alright!
This ain't fair.
You're right.
It ain't.
She's wearing a set
of legos on her head.
Hey it's a beefeater.
I'll buy you a gin
and tonic after this.
Looks kind of like Goofy.
Bonehead.
(robots chuckling)
Good one.
Geez, they should take
better care of their pets.
Hey that's not a museum
that's the cover of
the Far Side gallery.
You know this sport's a lot
better when played outside.
I claim this planet
in the name of Mars.
You know, I should
take up modeling,
I've got great cheekbones.
I'm still here, Happer.
You craphound.
Luke I am your father.
Surely you joust.
- Oh, and he picks up a spare!
- Rib.
That's coming out
of your allowance
until you pay back Michael
Jackson every last cent!
Cycles with wolves.
Oh she'll never look
for me under here.
Comedy chattering.
(chattering)
Mr. Henning's illusions
are accomplished
without the aid of
camera trickery.
What's he doing?
- I don't wanna know.
- Grooming.
Oh!
Yep, have a nice
trip, see you next fall.
I have no lines here.
Hey, those jazz dance classes
are really paying off!
(squeals)
Oh, it's a pizza cutter.
Should I cut it Chicago style?
Yeah!
Hail Dorothy, the
wicked witch is dead!
Hail Dorothy.
Here at studio 14
the Munsters Today is filmed.
Come back later,
the wizard is busy.
I feel like a happy king!
Thomas Heward Edward Cat.
These people are not animals.
They're not actors.
Well I admit what
we've seen here
is a certain element of--
What?
Barbarism?
Okay, barbarism, fine.
Fine, it's great!
What Mr. Carver talk is
useless with these people.
These people were born here.
Sorry, Sizzler for
lunch again everybody?
Thank you.
Sizzler okay with you guys?
Oh great, only the
fourth time this week.
I'm disappointed Ray.
Why must he always torture me?
It's the Bil Baird marionettes!
Wow, wow.
Helen,
I can sympathize
with your feelings.
But you're
contractually obligated
to finish this film.
- Progress.
- That's what my career lacks.
Is a train.
You can climb aboard,
you can get out of the way.
Or you can be crushed.
What it's like
being a has-been?
This train isn't stopping.
Those mischievous DAs
they ordered 1000
pizzas to their address!
(men mumbling)
Things take time!
We're out of time, Ray.
Ah, the foot!
Oh, foot, ow ow ow.
Hey that's not old Milwakee
it's Colt 45.
The beer that made
the truck famous.
Hey I can't find the
snow for the next scene!
Woah!
Don't bring him down.
Whitey!
(grunting)
You guys give me a hand.
(Joel humming)
Oh that's the thanks I get--
It's Hayley Mills in
where cable workers
go trouble follows.
(Whitey cackling)
Robin Hood, prince of thieves.
(robots chuckling)
Oh that super Dave Osborn,
really cracks me up.
Come on Mr. Wellander,
get back up there.
You're over the line, Whitey.
Guns are for scrows, Ray.
Besides it's a
waste of good beer.
Are you alone?
Well, I'm seeing
someone, if that, ah.
Be careful, these guys
are trained cable installers.
Yeah, Ray.
I'm alone, I'm alone.
(burping)
No wonder you're
alone, what a pig.
It's crude but funny.
I wanna show you
something, Ray.
(gun shooting)
We're done playing around.
Uh oh, the
principal heard that.
What, what?
I was kidding!
I was kidding I'll clean it up.
What were you saying
about the train?
I forget now.
Day one, day two,
day three, day one.
God I loved his bike.
His bike.
Et tu, Brutus?
Hey they're taking
his training wheels off.
Oh that proves, the
romance of David Bowie
and Mick Jagger.
Hey it's Jay Schroeder.
Jack be nimble.
All of a sudden
De Niro shows up.
Oh I saw this in JFK.
♪ And dance by the
light of the moon
♪ What did you wish for
when you threw that rock?
(crickets chirping)
Crickets?
He looks like Ed
Begley Jr. alright.
You got ideas, Lee?
Nope, my puzzler hurts.
Sure, I got lots of ideas.
I thought of fish sticks once.
- Good.
- Keep them to yourself.
Cause I'm all out.
Wanna get some ice creams?
Hey great dialogue!
Lenscrafters, Kim Cattrall,
in about one hour.
(keyboard clicking)
Will you quit being
evil over my shoulder?
(beeping)
It's really slow,
must be system seven.
Come on.
Oh, there's your punch.
Bingo.
We gotta get Windows
for this thing.
Oh get temps, it's easy.
Hmmm.
I've always had a great
deal of respect for you.
But now I'll have to kill you.
You're doing a
hell of a job but-
You look like a guy.
Do you understand?
No.
You know she only
has those glasses
so she can pull them
off dramatically.
I like it.
Let me put it to you this way.
(robots purring)
You go to your room
and you stay there.
Do you understand that?
But all I've got is an alcove.
Then you go to your
alcove and you stay there.
By tomorrow morning
this'll be history.
- Ok, Superman?
- Uh, DC.
Of course.
Mighty Thor?
Marvel!
Little Audrey?
Oh, burn it.
Hey say, shouldn't
we be carefully placing
these comic books
in plastic bags?
No, we have lives.
- Hey what you doing?
- Don't touch, stay away!
Jeepers, sorry.
Oh I get it, based on today's
rapid comic book culture
and today's experiment
you two have gone back through
your comic book collection
to find the meaning
of life, I get it.
No no, we found that,
that's that pile.
It's the Desert Aromic
Comic, dell version.
Yeah and it's packed
with action sequences.
(machine gun impersonations)
You are a child of
the universe, now die!
Go placidly amid
the noise and haste?
I don't think so!
Oh I see, since you can
make a comic book about--
Nuhuh, graphic novel.
Oh I see, since you
can make a graphic novel
about just about anything
why don't we come up with
our own super heroes?
Oh, I got one,
it's called Man Man.
He's bestowed with all
the powers of a man,
but he's a man.
I've got an idea, how about--
Oh wait wait wait,
maybe Man Man draws his
strength from Robert Blythe.
That's pretty good.
How about lumber man?
He controls the
forces of lumber!
Angle to route
lumber supplies,
to different parts
of the country
with his sidekick, Woody.
He defends the rain forests,
yet even he finds
Sting annoying.
(giggling)
Hey I've got an idea,
why don't we come up
with the super group
of all super heroes?
Like the Fantastic Four?
- Bigger!
- Twelve?
I know, I know.
The Fantastic 85!
Yeah!
Starting with Elbow Man!
Yeah, how about Mr. Papercut?
47 different angles of paper
jut from his body.
- Oh, the Punisher!
- There is a punisher.
Oh well this is a
new sort of punisher,
he's not overly strict, he just
sends people to their rooms.
The lint attachment man!
Jazz trio man, able to
trade fours with himself.
The human dog.
Professor Hitler and his
invisible knee machine.
Really Deep Man, he's
really deep man.
Or the Pheasant Plucker,
and the Pheasant Plucker's son.
The black nun, all black,
none of the white bits.
Always Smells like Maple Man.
The awesome power of
Absorbing Senior!
(alarm buzzing)
We've got movie sign!
(frantic yelling)
Serbo-Croatian Boy.
Calamari Man.
Butter Cats.
Foam Face.
Mrs. Martian.
They had the change to get
in line, they didn't take it.
You can't just cut
them down like this.
- Watch me.
- The school needs the band!
I can get you what
you want, I know it.
Back stage passes?
Let me at least try!
Ok.
If not you can take it
back and get what you want.
They either cooporate,
or they're dead!
Nice Nicotene patch.
Thanks I needed that.
High ho.
The Macy's parade,
15 years from now.
That's next year, get it.
Oh yeah, hey, current.
Shriner's pass and review!
Hey it's the big
municipal bike round up
and safety check!
It's all wrong.
Yes it needs some
mauves and some teals.
How come Kim gets
such a boring wardrobe?
Cause Kim's so boring?
No!
Hey wait a minute,
something's amiss,
where's my Robbie Benson poster?
There's got to be a
way out of this film!
The seven mercury astronauts!
It's Conrad Berty.
Hi black guys.
Hi hellow guys.
You know that roll bar's
not gonna be much
help in an accident.
Those are all the guys who
missed out on the master ninja.
Trust the Gorton's fisherman.
I am curious yellow.
That's quite a
bobby pin there, Kim.
Norton, outta there!
Oh so it all comes together now.
- Yes.
- S W 548.
It's so hard getting
around London.
Oh I get it she's
in the Chunnel.
The Chunnel of Chili?
I'm not eating
the ton of chili.
♪ Born to be wild
The Mild Ones.
Medea?
Medea Man, that's it.
I resent that.
Still carrying that torch.
You're fired, scarecrow!
Super Scarecrow.
Hey, you're supposed
to emulate someone,
not immolate them.
Johnny Kingsford,
edges light quickly.
I am the God of hellfire
and I bring you!
(robots humming)
You know the kid'll eat
the middle of the
sewer cover first.
And leave Kim
Cattrall for Crow?
Kim's having my
fantasy about her.
Oh, wow!
- Hey, it's
the NBC mystery movie.
- Would you stop that?
You guys, every time
you see a flashlight
it's not the NBC mystery movie.
You programmed us, weiner.
Kim Cattrall for first alert.
Mr. Goodbar?
Come on, Kim, come on,
you gotta want
it, come on, push!
Super Kim.
You bet.
(motorcycle revving)
Blanche, no!
Listen to me.
I'm the Sunday
night mystery movie!
I've just come from Sunya.
You picked a bad
time to come here.
They're gonna kill Mick.
The rat patrol, in color.
Uh oh, Sonny Rollins
is at it again.
The night belongs
to Old Milwaukee.
I think that guy's got
a Napoleon complex.
Super Bonaparte.
We gotta get more
theme costumes,
these guys are
kicking our butts.
(Crow whistling)
Crossfire.
You gotta come with us, Mick.
Green sleeves!
(laughing idiotically)
Those police bros are serious.
I'm talking to you, Mick!
Sleep!
I know I'm foppish.
- I got them to wait.
- Underweight?
Try a sport shake, they
have a whole stick of butter
in every can.
Mick, I couldn't do
nothing about Whitey.
Hey that's a double
negative, get him!
Looks like Belushi.
(screaming)
Shoot him down, shoot to kill.
(gunshots)
A little like a
turkey shoot, ye-hoo.
Rae Dawn, no!
Bay City Roller Man.
It's Henry the fifth.
(guns firing)
You got my little pants dirty!
Oh now, Mark
Lindsay's been hit.
Start seeing motorcycles.
Saved by a jawbreaker helmet.
Oh I wish I'd worn my
bullet proof cod piece.
Hey, Theresa Russel.
Now ride, David, ride!
Fonzie, no!
You know, the carnage
is beautiful from up here.
I tire, I'm going home.
Next week, on City Limits.
You know, that
coulda gone better.
Hey, our gondola
driver's dead.
Whoa, Rogaine out of control.
I don't see Mick.
He's a Q-tip.
Get away from him.
He's lost a lot of blood.
- Shut up.
- I can stop the bleeding.
There's nothing
wrong with him.
- Yogi.
- Yeah, Boo Boo?
(robots giggling)
Your Popsicle melted.
Who'd have thought the old
man to have so much blood?
It's ok, it's gonna
be ok, it's gonna be ok.
Somewhere there's a
clown missing a sleeve.
Tourniquet, I
coulda done that.
I wish I were a fish.
(sirens ringing)
Jim Henson's Rae
Dawn Chong babies.
Wait, is this happening now?
Or 15 years ago,
which would be now?
Same thing happened
to me out there, funny.
Should I reweave my hair?
I should pick up the
place but I'm tired.
Hi, whatchya doin?
Gimme a hand.
What we're doing here, Bob,
is taking out the old plumbing.
Hey it looks like
someone found a
ronco rhinestone
and stud setter.
- What are you doing?
- We need wheels.
- We got wheels.
- We got two bikes, smart.
There's three of us.
Four.
I'm in!
Yogi, I want you
to go to Pikes.
Mick.
Don't, just
listen for a change!
I'll meet you later
at the station.
At the Shining Time Station?
Pull that wire out of there.
Works every time.
He can really deliver a line.
Just like old
times, huh Sinch?
Oh, well you didn't
used to hit me like that.
Hey can I do one?
Ow.
Hey what did I miss?
Come on!
Get their clothes.
Hey look, I'm really happy
with what I'm wearing now.
No acting beyond this point.
Not allowed.
The illegal
smuggling of mimes.
Nobody talks about it.
Our soil and green
tour begins here.
Hey don't hassle me!
They got all the clippers.
Come on, let's go.
What are you, Gallagher?
It looks like cough syrup.
(Joel tsking)
It looks like a Vic's
formula 44 wipe out.
Oh they're gonna
spank him, oh look.
Oh it's American Gladiators.
Wait wait, it's me!
Annie Hall?
Whose idea was this?
- I learned it from you, Mick.
- Where'd I learn it?
Ride with me.
I got my own bike.
I'm guessing it's closed.
Uh, we're not open yet!
Kids, no bikes in the house.
Mick, there's something
I gotta tell you.
I said butter, not guns!
Mick, there ain't not bullets.
Aren't any, Rae, aren't any.
See, still works.
He is a master
of the universe,
no less than the trees.
Mick, what is it?
It's taffeta,
what do you think?
It's done.
Hey!
Ernie.
Hey Bert.
When's Robbie
Benson coming back?
Tell Ray I wanna see him.
You can call him Ray,
or you can call him Jerry,
or you can call him Sunny.
What are you looking at?
If I'm not back in an
hour you're on your own.
Order without me.
Hey, you're Kim Cattrall.
Minneapolis, after
the Super Bowl.
Mick you've gotta quit.
It's a dirty habit, man!
You leave, you go somewhere.
No deal, huh?
- We're doing good, Mick.
- Well, doing well!
They need us.
They would have used you too.
- Used is right.
- Oh, get off it Mick.
Open your eyes.
Look at you.
Junior achievement works!
This is a Sunya
town, you know.
Yeah.
Hey it's the Bart system.
Mick, go!
It's a Days Inn courtesy van.
Hi, I'm your Monsanto
representative.
Ray, would you see that Ernie
gets something to eat?
And I'm the sailor
with a difference.
Ok.
Boy that helmet's
been everywhere.
I'm filled with secrets!
Ok, thanks, what do
I owe you for the ride?
What a dope.
- I'm dead now.
- I'm Dead Boy.
Oh that chair's
got a bad spring.
Let's not drag
this out any longer.
Ernie told us all
about the gas station
but they aren't there any more.
They left you, Mick.
(spitting)
Bingo!
(grunts)
Alright, alright.
Wasn't a greenie.
Let's go in and catch
the end of the Cubs game.
A nice location for
a beating, isn't it?
Scenic.
Come on, Mick,
she killed Whitey.
Yeah, what about Lumpy?
You didn't know that.
Where's Wickings?
I'm right here!
How about a little
fire, scarecrow?
Super Dave, no!
Super Dave.
Oh, it's dumb.
Oh now, can we all just stop
and look at our scripts?
Oh, I guess it does
say that Boy George
drives in lobbing
Molotov cocktails, huh.
- It's a lasso wrap.
- What a drag.
Switcher!
You are one sick puppy.
(Crow singing)
Hey, it's the
Sunday night mystery
movie night gang!
There's Columbo, Snoop sisters.
Would you cut that out, Alvin!
Sorry, Dave.
Aw heck, Ramsey.
Start seeing motorcycle movies.
Great, they lapped the plot,
we're back at the beginning!
Oh man, we just went
in a big circle,
wake up we're at Grandma's.
Fashions by Maude.
God'll get you for that, Joel.
Take a shot at him.
(gun firing)
Oh, my kneecap exploded!
You'd think he'd see that
coming, it happened already.
It was just a love shot, my man.
From the love gun.
This is C, oh you know.
Where are we?
Back at the
beginning of the movie.
How many dogs do
you think he killed
to get that coat?
Plenty.
Hi, come on in.
Damn boy, I told
you to find adventure.
I didn't say drag it home.
Oh, you implied it.
These are the clippers.
Hey, you're Kim Cattrall.
Hey, who invited the stinky guy?
Smells like pussy nibbles.
Looks like Raising Arizona now.
Morning on Yasgur's farm.
(birds chirping)
What is this, pantsless
motorcycle repair?
Strip motorcylce.
Crab nuts, anybody?
Oh it's still too hot,
gotta take off more clothes.
Playing center, Chong,
Rae Dawn Chong.
Do you wanna take off
your pants and join me?
Was that you,
did you just caw?
Next week on Gabriel's Fire.
There is no next week
on Gabriel's Fire, Jim.
I haven't really
thought about it.
[James Earl Jones]
Well, you ought to.
The longer you wait.
The better she looks.
(robots coughing)
Man, she's got no pants
and he's got no shirt,
they barely have one
outfit between them.
Oh, it's a kickstart.
I'll never finish this.
Wanna do something about her?
Where was I?
Hi, I'm Martha
Ray, the big mouth.
Hi.
Let a smile be your umbrella.
There's a whole
in this casing.
I know that.
Boy, it was windy last night,
the cow's stuck
right to the barn!
So, so what?
So I'm stuck here.
Well I was just gonna say,
Tina Turner wants
her dress back.
You been in the barn?
No.
Well come on.
Guy like I'm so sure it stinks
in there and stuff.
Super Rae Dawn Chong.
(robots mooing and neighing)
Is there anything
living in here?
Well there's
probably microorganisms
living in here if you
wanna get technical.
- Nice, huh?
- Gary Busey sold it to me.
It's a 1948 Indian
Boneville Chief.
That's my mother dear.
- Can I?
- Yeah go ahead.
See it's got the
left hand throttle.
Oh I've got the best
sweater to go with this.
But I think you'll
be more interested
in something like this!
(screams)
What are you?
(stuttering)
Sing it, it works
for Mel Tillis.
Do you like this one?
Would you like this bike?
Sure, we all would!
Yeah, go ahead.
Roll it out.
It's the adventures
of ultra geek.
It's the wackiest
motorcycle in the army!
[Robots and Joel]
Wah-wah-wah-wah.
That's the stupidest thing
I've ever done in a movie.
We have so much fun laughing
at the misfortune of others.
Mick, you ain't in no
shape to be going any place.
- I'll manage.
- Where we going?
Crazy, wanna come?
Just me.
Well, me and my
swarthy friend here.
Thinkin about heading north.
[Guy on motorcycle]
I got a right, don't I?
I have my rights,
it was Callahan!
There is no us.
Not anymore.
That's kind unfair, hey.
You're wrong.
I'm gonna go get a shirt.
Aw, look, it's little
man Tate, how cute.
Dad, can we eat in the car?
Uh, can I get you
another root beer?
Anything else, more rings?
Um, we're out of toilet paper,
I'm gonna go into town.
Hey anybody for a ganip ganap?
Sorry, or something like that?
Hey come on, let's go
into twin like putt putt.
Anyone seen my
Sergeant Spike comics?
Somebody wanna watch
Mannequin with me again?
Super Mannequin.
Hey don't play with
the remote control dog.
You want something?
I can pick you off from here.
No.
Could you do a little scene
from Shakespeare for us,
it's getting kind of boring.
Oh Sergeant Spike
and Leather Woman.
Whoa, Harry Connick's
girlfriend, yeah.
Super Harry
Connick's Girlfriend.
I, um--
Ran out of checkered shirts.
Thought I'd try and
hitch a ride back east.
(soft piano music)
Um, like, I was wondering
could I play some of
your Bread records?
Look I really
wanna get through
this Richy Rich comic book, so.
There's probably
traffic on the road.
Traffic?
It's after the apocalypse.
Alright, get in, but don't
mess up the comic books.
I could find work.
It's after the apocalypse,
nobody's hiring.
Did I come at a bad time?
Hold me closer, tiny dancer.
Another company.
Another town.
Roar of the grease bed,
smell of the crowd.
Well we can all see he's
toned, tan, and terrific.
This is boring,
let's get out of here.
Hey I've got a good one.
Super Dana Andrews
and Velvet Woman.
Super Sim Cattrall woman.
Super Sim Cattrall?
(doors closing)
Easy does it with
Twelve Step Man!
The Middle Aged Boy.
The incredible adventures
of Bobby van Luke
and his radioactive
sweater vest!
Madam Velgary Man.
Are we up to 85 yet?
Did I say fantastic 85?
I meant fantastic 185.
Yes!
Perfect Paul and
his magnetic spleen,
he has only one flaw.
The girl who smells
like soda crackers.
Uncle Roger, the
airline steward man.
Porter Wagner.
Don't you mean
Super Porter Wagner?
No!
Super Fanny Bryce.
The clam.
Steak Face and Weasel Woman.
Doctor Doorknob
and his incredible
electromagnetic thing!
We have commercial sign,
but you should run on
ahead we'll be there.
Burger Chef!
He's incredi-burg-able.
Larry King.
Just Larry King?
He'd need a really good guest.
What are you doing?
How about Johnny Actionfinger?
He says he's going back.
Are you gonna go alone?
I'll go.
From now on call
me Lauren Green.
- Richie?
- Cunningham?
You got ideas, Lee?
Nope.
Yeah I got lotsa ideas, man.
He's got his goggles on.
Hey, lemme in on
it, what's going on?
Let's do it.
(robots humming)
Oh suddenly it's Flashdance.
It's more like Animal House,
so it's gonna say eat me
on the side of that thing.
Oh, behave.
I'm putting streamers
on my handle bars.
I'm putting cards in my spokes.
Action figures
sold separately.
(gun firing)
When I grew up
and went to school
there were certain teachers
who would shoot the children.
- Hurt the children.
- Sorry.
Got that Nitrous for
you, Mr. Earl Jones,
coming right up.
And this is me
with Anthony Zerbe.
(Crow beatboxing)
Oh, it's like MacGyver isn't it?
Oh I was just stalking her,
it's okay really.
Hey look, Archie Bunker's chair.
- Say, Lee.
- Yeah?
I gotta ask a question.
That car, is it yours?
No, it's Albert's.
- Lee, Billy was wondering...
- Why'd you take this role?
How the hell did
he get it in here?
Well it showed in
1961, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66.
The car was here first.
Get it?
Oh, Rosey Grier.
Oh not every man who
sews is Rosey Grier.
The New Power Generation!
Hello shoil.
And introducing
Gunther Cable Williams.
It's Jem, ooh!
Now has everyone gone pottie?
We're not stopping.
Come on, Malcolm
Farms is waiting for us,
let's go!
You know if you've
got kids who ride hogs,
you're gonna have stains.
Hey don't laugh,
it's paid for.
Bulletproof Vespas, in color.
(robots mooing)
Whoa!
Hey Suzanne Summers was in that.
Cadillac goldbottom 95.
Hey they brought
piffy with them.
Smart.
Bruce Jenner!
He's got a Picasso
boob platter on.
Oh, he kinda does, doesn't he?
These comic books are
getting kinda silly.
Hey do you hear something?
Something wacky
this way comes.
Hey it's the Sunday
night mystery--
Shut up!
Stop it.
Oh look, it's Sonny
Corleone's last destination.
They broke my booth!
That's the same
scene as before.
Rip off!
It's like he wants to order
a pizza but doesn't dare.
99 bottles of
beer on the wall.
Oh, you never wanna have fun.
This is great, this
is my James Earl Jones
books on tape.
(rock music playing)
Hey there's a
dumpster following you.
Hey it's Steve Guttenberg in
Don't Tell Her it's Me.
Sounds like U2 is
playing on the roof.
They still haven't found
what they're looking for.
Oh, you'll come and
open this sea, Norton.
Oh yikes, it smells
like a sewer down there.
(engine revving)
Then came boredom.
Oh, he shoulda thought
of that earlier.
Still got that rash?
Hey, they broke another gate!
Steven Seagal is
out for justice.
Switcher!
Oh, sorry, I was
looking for Soc. 101.
I'm taking over.
You ain't doing nothing.
(gun firing)
What a strict teacher.
Thank you, Albert.
I'm so sorry, Uncle Albert.
(students yelling)
Haha, works every time.
I hope you enjoyed
the Don Galloway
exhibit here at universal tour.
On your left is the studio
for the new Adam 12.
(students squealing)
School's out forever!
Oh no, it's terrible,
they're picking off
Gordon's fisherman.
Between classes at
inner city schools.
We decided to move
this scene back inside,
thanks, your cooperation
will be appreciated.
The cheese phone is back!
It's red and angry.
It looks like they
had to move the desk
to shampoo the rug.
Hello? Why won't anyone
do a scene with me?
(car radio playing)
Oh now it's American hot wax.
Boy, Days Inn really has
tight security these days.
Pardon me sir, excuse me.
Oh, gotta go.
Scuse me.
Hi there.
Hey they're having an
adventure like the Goonies.
Well it looks
like the milk truck
doesn't stop here anymore.
Well it says here
we can earn two dollars a day
picking apricots and peaches.
Lemme see that hand bill.
This way out of the movie!
This way.
You know I just can't take
him seriously anymore.
Not dressed like that.
If God's in heaven
he's driving a red Cadillac.
Whoa, James Earl Jones brought
the cooler everybody!
Look, I look stupid
I'm admitting that now.
Take care, ok?
He looks like Santa bear.
James Earl Jones,
ladies and gentlemen.
Let's give him a big hand.
(clapping)
Darn prop comics,
gotta bring their
stuff everywhere.
He's opening for Carrot Top.
I think Michelangelo
designed the scaffolding here.
It's Stalag 90210.
Oh, I've seen this,
this is the end of Planes,
Trains, and Automobiles.
Thank you for
calling Days Inn.
Look, Smithers,
I'm Davy Crokett.
Mr. Good Wrench, no!
That's a bad
wrench, right there.
What's in the box?
You needed that
huge trunk, for that?
You know one good thing
about the apocalypse,
always plenty of parking.
I still look great, I do.
Hey you wanna let us in
on your little personal joke?
Oh, they get to
play in the cistern.
Hey now everybody
remember where we parked.
A geometric nucleus.
Ok, everybody who's
gonna ride with me, hop in.
Ok we're at the last rest stop
before the end of our careers.
Oh, that's dirty pool.
If I knew what was going on,
I'd really be indignant.
Oh we'll just
let ourselves in.
Oh I'm being beat up
by the cast of
Pirates of Penzance.
Rex Smith.
Once I shot an
elephant in my pajamas.
Oh now we're in
The Man from Uncle
all of a sudden.
(grunting)
Heimlich maneuver,
what good is that?
And that's for not keeping
me up on script changes!
(Joel barking)
Sorry.
Hello Helen.
Oh hi, I was just
launching 1000 ships.
(robots singing)
It's the villain
from Johnny Quest!
I'm sure, that's so mean.
Scott Baio, no, no!
Kim, no! That's it.
Kill Roy and killjoy.
Huh?
Incoming model!
(explosion)
Jim Henson's flying
leather neck babies.
(Albert whistling Yankee Doodle)
Hey, it's worse that
the Roger Ramjet song.
Roger Ramjet he's our
man, hero of our nation.
Shazzam!
Hey, it sounds like
John Mayo just arrived.
- D'oh!
- Gilligan!
(robots coughing)
This is CNN.
There goes another one.
Come on you sons of bitches,
I'll shoot you down myself.
Turk, turk, turk,
turk what do we do?
Let us put you in the
driver's seat today.
(screaming)
Oh death with dignity, huh?
This is F. U. N.
I'm a prince on
the Grimwald Warrior.
See you next summer.
Carver!
Raymond Carver, if
we don't save him,
minimalism is doomed!
Don't I get a girl?
Jeez.
They just shot one of
the moment's shot guys.
No.
Point Break, 100
percent pure adrenaline.
Oh great, now
they're being attacked
by the Wooster Group.
Alright, Benson,
what the heck you been
doing in this movie?
If you eliminate me,
somebody just like me,
or even worse,
will follow.
One of the Carrety boys?
Ok, I was in Ice
Castles, I admit it.
I'm inevitable.
No.
Oh, these desk jobs
will just kill you.
Schmuckers jelly.
If you could taste
Robbie Benson.
On toast.
[James Earl Jones] So
the kids threw Sunya out,
and took over the running
of things instead.
Our team bills are ok, yay!
The DAs were joined.
And the city was in
the hands of its own.
And the kids born there,
and grown up there,
would make it work
for themselves.
Hey I hope your
leather Mustang
works out for you, huzzah!
Hey even the band is vomiting.
Darrell Larson is Mick.
Does that mean the
movie's gonna go on?
Since he is Mick?
John Stockwell is Lee.
No, is lame.
Kim Cattrall is
alright with me.
Rae Dawn Chong is wasted.
John Diehl is dangerous
to himself and others.
Yep that's my
name, that's my name.
Put her right there,
put her right there.
Don Opper is ashamed of himself
for writing the script.
And Norbert Weisser,
pleaded Bolo contendre
for having participated
in this film.
Frankie my dear,
I don't give a damn.
What you call hell,
Ramos calls home.
Dean Devlin is,
was, Michelle Shocked.
Oh, I don't know, how special
this was. I don't think so.
I know I've done
better, but look you can't
pay the rent doing
August Wilson plays.
So can we leave
now, Joel, please?
Uh, no, I think you
realize we have have to stay
through the closing credits.
What is that a
law or something?
Well it kind of is, it's
a mad scientist thing.
Oh no argument there,
you can't do much about that.
Pretty much just gotta cope.
No problem with that.
I guess it's ok.
- Do we have
to sit through these?
- Can we just please leave!
- Word up, blood?
- Hey homie.
The movie's lousy
you really can tell
the only thing I liked
was Kim Cattrall.
Kim, k-k-k-k-kim.
It was really stupid
it was way too long
It starred Robbie Benson
and Rae Dawn Chong.
I thought that
Sidehacking really was bad,
I thought the Mighty
Jack really made me mad.
I thought Pod People
really was a pit,
but the stupidest movie
was the biggest piece of--
Hey, check him out.
I'm just talking
about City Limits, Crow.
I wish I could
see Citizen Cane,
I wish I could see
Rule of the Game,
I wish I could
view Seven Samurai,
but every film I see
make's me wanna die.
Something going down
in this town.
Something in the air that
you can feel underground.
You know it's supposed
to really excite me,
but all I can tell
you is no, bite me!
Bite me, bite me.
(doors closing)
Ok, 2.
Ok.
- This way.
- No, that way.
Ok, roll again, ok.
Daddy needs a new
pair of hydrolic talons.
Joel is there a
point to this little
City Limits trivia game here?
The City Limits trivia game
was actually one of the
many promotional items
when the film came
out in theaters.
And they had lots of stuff,
they had this trivia game,
they had City Limits beefy tees,
they had City Limits eyewear,
they even had a City Limits
32 ounce promotional glass
at Subway,
it was a whole thing.
Come on, Joel, roll!
Ok, alright.
You see the problem
with the trivia game here
is I don't remember anything
from this experiment,
I mean nothing.
It just didn't stick with me.
I mean I even forget what
we're talking about right now.
Come on, roll
again, roll again!
Luck be a lady tonight.
Ok, you're in clipper
territory, Crow.
And I draw a James
Earl Jones card.
In the movie City Limits, Crow,
Ray Dawn Chong's
character's name was
A, Yogi, B, Yoda, C, Yoyo?
Uh, who?
Ray Dawn Chong,
she was in the movie.
Ray Dawn, Ray, hmm.
Oh, I'm sorry it's
not ringing a bell.
Was she the black
guy with a beard?
Ok, come on, Tom,
you do the next one.
Ok here's one.
Ok it's your turn, Tom.
In the movie, City Limits, Tom,
what was the name of the movie?
Oh jeez, it seems like
I oughtta know this one.
Swiss Family Robinson?
The Robe?
Helter Skelter?
Switch?
Jimmy's Fence.
Let's read a
letter, how bout it.
We put this up on still
story, you got that there,
okay, this is from
Joseph Jerrick
of Chicago Illinois.
He writes, MST3000
I would like to
join your information
club, thank you.
Terse, concise.
I like that Joe, keep it up.
Put that up on still
store and this one
is from Billy Jenson.
Dear MTS.
Wrong!
I like your show
because I like to laugh,
and at lots of jokes,
I'm sort of a comedian,
and a cartoonist.
Raconteur.
Here's a joke.
Point to your head and
say the abbreviation
of mountain.
M, T.
That's very logical, Billy.
Here's another joke.
What would you say to a
two headed monster, Crow?
Um.
Got me.
Hi, hi.
Ok.
That was cute Billy.
Polish the end
of the act there.
Do you wanna say--
I'll say the address now.
Send your letters to the MST 3K
Information Club.
Post Office Box 5325
Hopkins, Minnesota, 55343.
But be careful when
you send jokes, okay?
Oh, I got it.
(laughing)
What do think, sirs?
Well, Siegfried and Roy.
What?
Did I mention that I cried?
Yes you mentioned it!
Come on, Frank, take him out.
Come here, suedehead.
Until next time, Joel.